(Sheldon:)I'd be in my lair enjoying the money
the people of Earth gave me...
(Sheldon:)...for not using my death ray.
(Sheldon:)All right. And in three, two, one.
(Raj:)That is one tough birdie.
(Leonard:)Come on, you enjoyed the movie.
(Leonard:)I saw you tearing up when the village
flooded and everyone had to relocate.
(Penny:)No, I was thinking how come
they get to leave and I can't.
I'm gonna get some fries.
You want anything?
- Uh, no, thanks.
- Are you sure?
(Leonard:)Because you always say no,
and then you eat haIf my fries.
(Penny:)I just eat the little crispy ones
you don't like.
(Leonard:)No, I love them. I save them for the end,
but they're gone because you ate them.
(Leonard:)And why did I let you eat them?
(Penny:)- To get sex.
- Exactly.
(Leonard:)But this is not a date.
(Leonard:)So I ask again.
Would you like anything?
- All right. L'd like an order of fries.
- Great. That'll be 5 dollars.